{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Kuhn",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ohio",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Kuhn was born in Ohio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9298129677772522,
            "question": "Where was Thomas Kuhn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3318813145160675,
            "question": "Where did Thomas Kuhn work or teach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29582926630973816,
            "question": "What field of study was Thomas Kuhn involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18300777673721313,
            "question": "Did Thomas Kuhn have any notable mentors or influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1768622100353241,
            "question": "Is Thomas Kuhn known for any specific work or theory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16560137271881104,
            "question": "What state is Ohio located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15943801403045654,
            "question": "What were some of the key concepts in Thomas Kuhn's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1376790702342987,
            "question": "How did Thomas Kuhn's ideas influence scientific thought?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1352153867483139,
            "question": "What is Thomas Kuhn's most famous book titled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1255338042974472,
            "question": "What are some criticisms of Thomas Kuhn's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Kuhn was born in Ohio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7990_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Thomas Kuhn's most famous book titled?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7990_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Thomas Kuhn's ideas influence scientific thought?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7990_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the key concepts in Thomas Kuhn's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7990_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7990_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Thomas Kuhn was indeed born in Cincinnati, Ohio. This information is mentioned in multiple files (files 8, 22, 68). Therefore, the triple \"Thomas Kuhn was born in Ohio\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Thomas Kuhn was born in Ohio.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention that Thomas Kuhn was born in Cincinnati, Ohio."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}